Good morning. How y'all doing? Good to
see everyone. Um, obviously it's it's uh
been a tough couple days. Tough end of
the season. It's never easy, but it's
this is extra tough just, you know,
because we got so close. But um couldn't
be more proud of our players, our
coaches, our staff for everything, you
know, they achieved uh this season, you
know, advancing to the AFC Championship
game, number one seed, you know, won the
division for the first time in 10 years.
And you know, I think we won 11 straight
games. Um, won 14 regular season games,
which ties a team record. And really,
credit goes to Shawn and the winning
culture he's instilled since he arrived.
Uh, Greg and Carrie, you know, for their
leadership and all the resources they
led us to pour into our players. And
then, um, you know, when you have a
season like this, it takes a village.
And really, everyone in our
organization, I just want to thank for
all the hard work, uh, they put into
this season. Um, you know, when you look
back at this team, you know, this is a
special team. I I think I mentioned in
the preseason just they love the
process, they love the grind, uh, they
love the work. Um, this is as close as
team as I've ever been around. I think
you guys could probably feel that. You
could see that translate to the games,
you know, uh, never flinch, never say
die. This team just fought and so, you
know, remember this team, you know, for
that. Obviously, uh, we move forward
now. We're into our offseason. Um, our
scouts are at the senior bowl. they've
been at the East West. We'll do a deep
dive on this team like we do every year
and we'll determine our needs. We'll be
aggressive filling those needs. We know,
you know, you start over. You know,
nothing's guaranteed. This is a great
season. We move on and and just excited
for that challenge. And, uh, you know,
with that, I'll take your questions.
George, uh, you heard [snorts] in the
preseason Sean tell a number of people
that he thought this was a Super Bowl
caliber team and even though you come up
a little short, I guess how validating
is it that and I guess what was your
reaction when he said that and he's
putting it out there, but then
>> well, you know, he puts it out there,
you know, and he's it's a little
different than me, but that's Sean and
and that's everywhere he's been and and
typically he backs it up and and the
players I think they feed off that and
they feed off the energy. Uh, he's a
great motivator and um I think the whole
building feeds off it. you know, the
confidence is, you know, we haven't won
here in a long time. So to have someone
come in and say, "We're going to do
this." And he just says that one, he
says that to us every day. I mean, and
and shoot, you start believing it.
>> Uh George, you mentioned being
aggressive in the offseason. After
getting this close, getting to the AFC
Championship game, how do you evaluate
whether this roster just needs
refinement or some aggressive pushes to
get to that next step?
>> Yeah, that's a it's a good question. Um,
I think it just takes, you know, we'll
take a week of going through the roster,
you know, with a fine tooth and and go
through every position and and we
evaluate our our roster versus the other
rosters. Our roster versus the AFC West,
we'll stack, you know, each position and
and just determine where we need to get
better at. You know, every team needs to
get better and and there's no perfect
team and and so we'll spend a week at
least doing that and and then, you know,
again, who who's available, who's
available in free agency, who's
available in the draft. And so it's a
puzzle and and you have a plan and and
you hope to execute that plan.
>> Hey George, um Sean just talked about
sort of the capital you put into
drafting and the receiver room and all
that. Overall, do you feel like you have
enough playmaking ability? Sort of a
broad question, but receiver, running
back,
>> receiver, running back. Uh again, we'll
do a deep dive. I like our young
players. I like, you know, I like our
young receivers and u I think we drafted
three and you got Court and a little
Jordan. We got a good mix of players and
uh but we're always looking to add.
We're always looking to improve at every
position.
uh running back will do the same. You
know, I like the young the young backs
we have. JK was was a big hit here and
uh that was a big loss, you know, for
our team and our offense and and just
his leadership that he showed. So, we'll
look at everything. Um I think we have
some young talent and uh if we can add,
you know, we will and if we can upgrade,
we will certainly.
>> George Sher left, you mentioned this
time a year ago that you thought you had
a franchise guy in Bo Knicks. What did
you see from him in year two,
particularly in those [clears throat]
end of game moments like you talked
about?
I I just think you evaluate a
quarterback by how much he wins. And
there's been no quarterback in his first
two years who's won more than Bo. So, we
we can just start start there. And then
I think he had seven game-winning
drives. And it got to the point where
we're behind and Bo had the ball. We're
like, "Okay, this we're going to win
this." And and and you can look at all
the traits for quarterbacks and um their
arm strength, their act, you know, all
that. But, you know, I don't think you
can, you know, he has that it factor.
You know, I don't think you can teach
that that either you have it or you
don't. and he has it. And so, wow, you
know, two years we have a quarterback
that that can win win win at a high
level. Um, he's best in the big moments.
You know, we've seen that. Does he have
areas to improve? Yes, like all
quarterbacks. But if you have a
quarterback that has a it factor that's
best in the big moments, you know, that
that's pretty big.
>> Hey, George, you uh took some swings on
some free agents this year with some
some injury history. What's your
evaluation of that process as it goes
going forward with free agency?
Yeah, I think I think we have a really
good process. I think um you evaluate
each player differently. You know, you
don't want to bring in a bunch of, you
know, guys who've been hurt, but I you
know, with with Bo Lowry and our medical
department, we feel really strong about
their opinion. And um if someone's been
hurt someone else, you know, maybe we
feel like, you know, we can get them
going. We'll have a plan. Not that other
teams don't, but we just feel really
strongly about our medical team, our
sports performance team where we can
bring someone in our environment and
they can thrive. And uh you know I think
they have
>> George right here. Um Sean has talked
about your relationship with him and
only said great things except that you
spell your or you pronounce your last
name wrong. Um how has that partnership
been between the two of you especially
over these last two years with a rookie
quarterback and dealing with some dead
money?
>> Yeah, I always wanted a Y as a kid.
Walter Payeyton was my favorite player
and I had a you know but anyway I think
it's been good. It keeps growing. I mean
it's been outstanding. Um I think um
we met in our interview I think he
refers to that interview you know um in
Westlake and and and I knew then we we
would be aligned in how we wanted to
build this and that's just continued to
grow and and u you know how much he
loves the draft process, the personnel
process and and not only does he love
it, he's really good at it. I mean he's
really good. He knows what he wants. He
articulates it well to the to the all
the scouts. So we all know what a Denver
Bronco player at this position should
look like. uh his staff is really good
at it and so um we enjoy being around
each other. Um not always easy. It
shouldn't be easy. You know, winning is
not easy, but uh I just think it keeps
getting stronger. I'm very fortunate to
have him here with with me.
>> George, when you get that close,
people in the organization, do you
personally can you even watch the Super
Bowl?
>> Yeah, I think I think you do. I mean,
you know, right now I would say no, but
when we get there, I mean, we're we love
we love the game and there's nothing
like the Super Bowl and um so I think I
think we watch it. We all, you know,
I've talked a bunch bunch of players
yesterday and there's a bunch of players
waiting in my office right now and a lot
of them said they're not going to watch
it, but I know we'll all watch it. We
love this game and it's too important
and you envision yourself being there
one day, you know, and that's what, you
know, makes it special.
George, um, a couple of your your your
young defensive rookies, you know, we
saw Q Robinson m make an impact in the
game and then and then Jade as well.
What just sort of is your impression of
of kind of how that came along this
year?
>> All the rookies or just the defense
>> defensively?
>> Yeah, I I think Jade,
he played nickel, he played dime, he
played little corner. You can see all
the traits. You know, he he was um good
for us, probably not so good for him. he
was drafted maybe the deepest second,
you know, the corner back room in the
league and he made he made his mark and
he's just going to keep growing, keep
getting better. Um, you know, second
round was RJ, but I'll I'll stay with
the defense. And then Savon Jones,
again, we draft, we we really like where
he's going. You know, we see the
development in practice. I think he only
played 33 snaps, but he had four or five
pressures. He had a fumble recovery. Uh,
we knew he'd be, you know, a little
development, but this guy's big. He's
strong. He's athletic. He's going to be
a player. And then Q, I mean, he may be
the most have the most upside on our
draft class, and you could see it the
other day. I mean, he's he's long, he's
athletic, he can run. Um, really good in
the run game. Um, just learning how to
rush. Just learning how to rush the
passer, but has all the traits. And then
you see what he does on special teams.
So, really encouraged with him. And I
think that's all the defensive guys,
right, for that. Then we have two um
college, you know, free agent
linebackers we like. Cleavell Bailey um
who got a little taste and then uh
Jordan you know ta yeah Jordan Taylor um
who's really good on special teams.
>> Yeah George uh you were got a or two
years of the lean lean times here and uh
we're big in the turnaround. What were
some of the keys besides you know the
coach and quarterback ownership besides
those three things?
>> What else is there Mike? was you know
anything you know deeper dive into what
>> I I just think it's uh yeah tough times
you know when when you come come in an
organization you don't have success
right away I I think it's important to
stay true to what got you here stay true
to your process and then don't listen to
all the outside stuff um and then
encourage your staff to do the same and
just stay the course you know just just
keep going you know keep keep grinding
and uh you know we were fortunate
obviously to have this ownership group
um and then u to hire Sean and and I
think that turned it and then you know
obviously the quarterback and all the
other things.
>> George, you got two big things going for
you this year. You're out from under the
the deadcap charges from Russ and that
new facility. How is that going to
facilitate free agent signings?
>> Yeah, I think players will want to come
here for for a number of reasons. I
think uh number one is ownership. That's
the number one. And you can see what
they've done, what they're doing, what
they continue to do, and and all the
resources and and leadership they've
shown. Um, you know, I think, uh,
quarterback makes a big difference. You
players wanting to come to the
quarterback and and and the fan base in
Denver. I mean, people people love it
here and I think that that helps and and
you know, now we're playing at a high
level and and again, it starts over, but
I think uh I think players will want to
be here.
>> George, George, you're on the clock with
a rookie quarterback under that
contract.
getting this close, does that instill
that sense of urgency like this is kind
of that window? And how do you in
knowing Shawn now, how do you think
he'll deal with Sunday's disappointment
as fuel or has he he's used the word
regret, you know?
>> Yeah, we we've both been through this.
This is my third championship loss. He's
been through it. He's had tough losses.
You learn, you have to move forward. You
look at the things that we did, you all
the positive things that we did, and you
build on that. Um, you know, in regards
to the quarterback, I don't think we
that I mean, we're always going to push
it and we're going to push it this year.
You know, it's all these other teams are
pushing it. They're hiring these co, you
know, so we have to be on our game. We
have to make really good decisions.
We're going to be aggressive and uh
regardless of what, you know, whose
contract is what. I think it's really
important. Um, now we're going to be
sound and prudent with our decisions.
And the good news is, you know, we have
some cap room. We have all our we have
five picks in the first four rounds. We
could get two compensatory which would
give us nine. So we just have you know I
always talk flexibility. We're going to
have all sorts of flexibility.
>> You know we just keep we you know we
just stick to the process. You know I
don't get too far ahead of it. You know,
again, every year you start over and you
you you build in a sense and and we're
going to have to build in a sense, but
we just we just need to get better than
we were and and you know, we'll just
kind of stick with that.
>> George, uh that aggressiveness
retrospect, do do you maybe regret kind
of not making a bigger move for for a
wide out for a skill guy at the deadline
or or mid-season this year? And and is
that going to be something you look at
pretty as you mentioned aggressively,
you know, this offseason?
>> No, I don't regret that. I mean, at the
time we had a, you know, we like our
receiving group. You know, I don't think
I don't think our receiving group, you
know, held us back from this game. You
know, I don't I don't look at it like
that. Um, we got some young receivers
and Pat Bryant and Troy Franklin and and
Mimsy and and u and Sut, you know, I
don't think that's the reason we didn't
make the Super Bowl. I think those guys,
you know, in their own right, had had
good years. You know, we had some
injuries in the end that hurt us. You
know, going back to Buffalo, we had
three receivers, you know, for the rest,
you know, I think from the second
quarter on. That's tough. And then in
this game we had four. Um you know we we
always look at everything. I don't think
um you know what was available um you
know would have made much of a
difference you know for us but uh I
can't what was your second question?
That was it.
>> We'll we'll look at everything every
position. I appreciate that. Yeah.
>> George you touched on it but just
hearing guys yesterday like Alex
Singleton JK Dobbins be very vocal about
wanting to stay here. Do you like
hearing that? Does that kind of help
validate what you guys are building
here?
>> You do. You want your players, you know,
to want to be here. That's for sure. And
again, it starts at the top with the
ownership and and Shawn and what we're
building. And and you look at we get
players who come from other places and
you look at our our resources and the
modalities and and our, you know, our
sports performance team and and it's
it's it's an easy sell here. And then
they look at the new facility. Um,
obviously there's gonna be new stadium
down the road, but uh, yeah, this
ownership group is second to none.
>> Um, George, going back to Bo Nicks, what
was your evaluation on how the surgery
went in his health and his timetable? Do
you see him doing any work in OTAAS or
or so?
>> I mean, I think he's I think they said,
you know, close to May. I think he'll,
you know, um, I think he's going to be
fine. I think Sean talked about that.
Um, he's going through it. I mean, he's
in the building. Um, he's working every
day and he'll, you know, he'll be back.
I'm not sure the exact date. We feel
good about that.
>> George, you obviously got unrestricted
free agents, but Jac is a restricted
free agent. Obviously, he's turned
himself into one of the best players in
the game. Is he a extension candidate
type or what do you do when you have a
guy that's he's in sort of a unique
position, I guess?
>> Yeah, he's a restricted. Um,
>> great story. you know, Jay Mack, we got
him as a college free agent and and uh I
remember his first year we started him
outside against the Chargers in the last
game of year and I'm just like, "Oh man,
you know, he's 59. He's going to play
outside against his receivers and and he
played a great game and you're like,
"Wow, maybe we have something here." And
then he's just gotten better run game,
pass game, you know, we're going to work
through that, you know, as a staff, you
know, in that deep dive and kind of go
through that and just keep that in
house.